<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://mao3267.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://mao3267.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FoodiePlan</title>
      <link>https://mao3267.github.io/projects/foodieplan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mao3267.github.io/projects/foodieplan/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A meal planning web app built with Next.js, MongoDB, and Google OAuth. FoodiePlan leverages Gemini AI to generate personalized recipe suggestions and weekly meal plans based on user preferences, dietary restrictions, and available ingredients.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Research Assistant</title>
      <link>https://mao3267.github.io/experience/nlplab/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 21:50:20 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mao3267.github.io/experience/nlplab/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;the-beginning-of-my-llm-journey&#34;&gt;The Beginning of My LLM Journey&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Under the guidance of Prof. An-Zi Yen, I delved into a lecture-abstract-based question generation system project, where we fine-tuned an LLM on self-collected datasets. Our demo system&amp;rsquo;s performance has outperformed state-of-the-art models, and I led the authorship of a paper accepted at the International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI). Recognizing LLMs&amp;rsquo; challenges in performing complex reasoning and answering questions, we focused on error detection in math problems and achieved improvements through our proposed self-refinement framework.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Personal Website started!</title>
      <link>https://mao3267.github.io/blog/post%231/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 20:37:49 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mao3267.github.io/blog/post%231/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The idea of creating a personal website has been on my mind for several years. After much consideration and effort, I am excited to announce that I have finally launched my personal website! In the near future, I plan to publish engaging articles and blogs here.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I want to express my gratitude to Hugo and the many helpful blogs and videos that guided me through the process. Thanks to these resources, the very first version of my website is now live! My goal is to publish new blog posts every week to document my journey and share valuable insights.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>E-QGen: Educational Lecture Abstract-based Question Generation System</title>
      <link>https://mao3267.github.io/projects/eqgen/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 19:38:56 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mao3267.github.io/projects/eqgen/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A lecture abstract-based question generation system optimizing the preparation process for educators in academic lectures and associated Q&amp;amp;A sessions. Given a lecture abstract, E-QGen generates potential student inquiries. The questions suggested by our system are expected to not only facilitate teachers in preparing answers in advance but also enable them to supply additional resources when necessary. This demo paper was accepted by the International Joint Conference on Artificial Intelligence (IJCAI) 2024 at Jeju.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Flyte Open Source Contributions</title>
      <link>https://mao3267.github.io/projects/flyte/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 19:38:45 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mao3267.github.io/projects/flyte/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Collaborating with open-source community members worldwide to implement features and fix bugs strengthened my software development and communication skills, laying the foundation for contributing to large-scale projects. My contributions mainly focus on enhancing dataclass support and implementing features that strengthen the usability of Flyte and its python SDK Flytekit. Since now, I have contributed over 15 pull requests and 1000 lines of code.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Omnichat</title>
      <link>https://mao3267.github.io/experience/omnichat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 19:36:27 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>https://mao3267.github.io/experience/omnichat/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;empowering-possibilities-through-llms&#34;&gt;Empowering possibilities through LLMs&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;In my journey to expand the practical application of my LLM research skills, I took on an AI Research Internship at OmniChat, where I delved into the dynamic intersection of software engineering and natural language processing. During this role, I contributed to the development of an &amp;ldquo;AI Customer Service Chatbot&amp;rdquo; by integrating retrieval-augmented generation with automated workflows, creating an end-to-end chatbot solution. My work also involved incorporating LLM agents into existing systems to streamline audience targeting and promotional workflow creation using intuitive, natural language commands. These experiences not only deepened my technical expertise in large language models but also offered valuable insights into the challenges and intricacies of building and maintaining NLP systems in an industry setting. Through this role, I witnessed firsthand the transformative impact of retrieval systems and LLM agents in solving complex problems and enhancing access to information.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
